idealist4ever.com 2017-06-11

# Privacy policy – Idealist 4 Ever

## Section 1 – How your information is used

Most websites collect information from their visitors. This includes IP address, browser type, and referring page. Cookies are used to remember the visitor’s preferences for interacting with the website. That said, the information Idealist Revolution gathers will be used to enhance the visitor’s experience and may be used to target advertising. Your email address will not be sold to third parties, but if provided, your email may be used to inform you of news from us and to receive discounts/give-aways from vegan friendly companies.

## Section 2 – Consent

If you provide us with any kind of personal information, it is implied that you’re consenting us to collect it. If we request additional personal information for a secondary reason, marketing for example, we will ask you directly for your consent, or give you the opportunity to say no.

## Section 3 – Our disclosure requirements

If we are required by law to disclose your personal information, we do reserve that right.

## Section 4 – Links

Any time you follow a link from our website to another, we aren’t responsible for the privacy policies of those other sites. We encourage you to read their private policies. Additionally, we use Google Analytics to help us learn about you, the visitor! It doesn’t tell us too much, just what you’ve been checking out on the site.

## Section 5 – Third-party services

Third-party groups will only be allowed the information voluntarily collected from you to allow them to provide a service to us (see: advertising). We will not sell your email address to third parties under any circumstance.

## Section 6 – Age of consent

By using this website, you acknowledge that you are the age of consent in your state, province, or country, or that you are a consenting adult giving consent to a minor to use this website.

## Section 7 – Changes to this policy

We reserve the ability to change this privacy policy at any time, so review it frequently. Changes take effect immediately upon posting on this website unless otherwise specified.

## Section 8 – Questions

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policies, please send an email to [HiheartsDating@gmail.com](mailto:hiheartsdating@gmail.com)

## Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
